# TYLER KOTLOWSKI

# SKILLS

I am a Researcher foremost, Data Analyst, Django Framework, Web Developer and Python Programmer. I've learned many skills, trades, and practices. I am useful in many areas to provide upmost efficiency to those around me. I am a great team member and leader.

# EXPERIENCE

# LOASM Technician | USAF | 2012 - 2014

Worked on F-22 stealth aircraft structures for the Air Force.

#### Welder | Relco | 2014

Welded food grade stainless for cheese manufacturing companies throughout Wisconsin, Minnesota, and Pennsylvania.

#### Electrician | Friendship Homes | 2014 – 2015

Worked with raw wiring in mobile homes, including, light fixtures, appliances, circuitry, and other electrical component installations.

#### Insurance Agent | Independent | 2015 – 2016

Worked primarily with supplemental insurance and partly with major health plans. Worked with the design/sales of a new insurance platform tool that helped drive business higher.

#### Computer Specialist | Best Buy | 2017 – 2017

Worked with all things computers and accessories for mobile devices as well as desktops and laptops. Helped diagnose customer needs and wants and mainly used this job as an experience builder.

# Programmer | 2016-Present

Github - https://github.com/Nanonzt

Trading Analyst | Advisor | 2017-PRESENT

# OBJECTIVE

Why hire me? Because I can do many things. I have learned many traits, skills, tools, and knowledge to be incredibly effective at all that I do. If I don't have the answer, I'll find it. I look for patterns, rhythms, series of things, to create more effective paths of execution. I'm more than your average joe.





Best Method
Nano.nzt Gmail

Work (320) 321-4938

# VOLUNTEERING

I've done environmental clean up in most cities I have lived in. I have volunteered time as security for multiple festivals in Alaska for USAF promotion purposes.

I am a USAF Active Duty Veteran.
I am also an ambassador/advisor to multiple cryptocurrency projects.

# EDUCATION

# HS Diploma | 2012 | YME

# LOASM Cert | 2013 | USAF

Received many aircraft structural certifications. Stealth technology certifications.

Secret clearances.

# Welding Cert | Aug 2014 | Ridgewater, Willmar MN

Graduated 2<sup>nd</sup> in program out of 10 participants. Learned blueprints, architecture, scale models, MIG, TIG, and Stick welding. Most proficient in TIG welding.

#### Health and Accident Insurance License | 2015

Minnesota major health license, supplemental insurance license.

# Python | 2017-Today | Florida Institute of Technology

Currently building with Python for data analytics/mining, GUI applications, and webscraping.

#### Other Skills and Languages

R, Django, Unity 3D, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Java

# PROGRAMMING // PROJECTS

#### --Clide--

Al Personal Assistant

# --Sal--

Automated File Merging Program

#### --Global Ocean Pollution Research--

Working with R and Unity to produce a real-time animation of the oceans plastic pollution.

(Development)

# --Cryptobot--

Bitcoin trade-bot, automates off my personal trade habits. (Testing)

#### INTERESTS

Python/R programming in my free time.

I research cryptocurrency projects and technology.

I spend time with my wife and kids.
I learn new skills.

# GOALS

To live a life of knowledge.

Contribute to great projects.

To retire earlier than most.

# REFERENCES

#### Adam Savariego

Long Time Friend / Advisor (320) 226-5082

#### **Jerry Streitz**

Advisor (320) 761-3106

#### Carlos Esquibel

Long Time Friend (320) 226-8358